Guide to the Paper Tiger Television Archive, ca. 1981-2014 MSS.276
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Publicity
  - Subseries A: Press
    - Vancouver Sun, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Variant - Glasgow, Scotland, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Vidéazimut, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Video Classics, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Video Data Bank - profile, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Video Networks, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Video Popular - Brazilian magazine, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Video Times - Marisa Bowe article, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Video Times - Independent's Day, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Village Voice mention, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Village Voice mentions, 1982-1989 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Village Voice - Taubin article, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Village Voice - Social Engagements and other mentions, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Villaga Voice - Lucy Lippard article, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Visions - journal, 1985-1991 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Washington City Paper - Cyberspace, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Washington Post / Washington Times reviews, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Whitney Museum and Gusto - articles, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Win Magazine, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Wired / Cyberspace, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - World magazine - Pittston review, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Z Magazine, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Zebra magazine, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Subseries B: Promotion
    - 9/11 Actions and action related promotion, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - Access Orbit program description book, Undated (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Ads in radical mags, Undated (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - Ad slick originals, Undated (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - Ads - PTTV, Undated (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - AK press folder (labels), Undated (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - Billboards of the Future - sent by Stuart Ewen, Undated (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Book distribution flyers, Undated (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - Casualties of War - flyers, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - Catalog - master negative, Undated (Box 16, Folder 65)
    - Christian Right distribution, Undated (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - Daily News flyer, Undated (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - Deep Dish TV flyers and promotion, Undated (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - Deep Dish TV - mailers, Undated (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - Deep Dish TV - schedule, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - Deep Dish TV - schedule, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - Drawing the Line at Pittston - flyers and quotes, Undated (Box 16, Folder 72)
    - Flyer masters, Undated (Box 16, Folder 73)
    - Flyer and schedule masters, Undated (Box 16, Folder 74)
    - Flyers - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 16, Folder 75)
    - Flyers - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 16, Folder 76)
    - Flyers - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 16, Folder 77)
    - Flyers - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 16, Folder 78)
    - Flyers - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 16, Folder 79)
    - Flyers - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 16, Folder 80)
    - Flyers - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 16, Folder 81)
    - Flyers and pamphlets - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 16, Folder 82)
    - Flyers and pamphlets - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Flyers and pamphlets - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Flyers and pamphlets - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Flyers and pamphlets - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Flyers and pamphlets - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Flyers - old PTTV mixed, Undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Flyers - PTTV informational, Undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Fundraising flyers, Undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - General publicity and outreach materials (1 of 3), Undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - General publicity and outreach materials (2 of 3), Undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - General publicity and outreach materials (3 of 3), Undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Gulf Crisis TV - events, flyers, and press, Undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Gulf Crisis TV - flyers, Undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Gulf Crisis TV - flyers, Undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Gulf Crisis TV - flyers and promos, Undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Gulf Crisis TV - flyers from second series, Undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Gulf Crisis TV - pamphlets, Undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Gulf Crisis TV - posters, Undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Gulf Crisis TV - press file, Undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Gulf Crisis TV - promotion with press originals, Undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Hinkley's Believe it...or Else! flyers, Undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Letters collage, Undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Masters - informational mailers, Undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Mailings, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - NYC public access schedules, Undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Original flyer for first show, Undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Paper Tiger TV benefit party, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Paper Tiger TV - Cat-a-log, Undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - "Paper Tiger DVD's: $25" sign, Undated (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Paper Tiger TV newsletter, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Paper Tiger TV newsletter - advertising and activism, Undated (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Paper Tiger's Paper Money, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Paper Tiger TV Presents: A Special Conference Offer, Undated (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Paper Tiger TV - San Francisco flyers, Undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Paper Tiger TV - selected shows, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Press Release - Access Orbit Youth Satellite series, Undated (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Press Release - Check Point '95: The Bridge Project, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Press Release - Gulf Crisis TV, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Press Release - Herb Schiller Reads The New York Times, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Press Release - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Press Release - Move to Gallery 345, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Press Release - Tape sale and rental, Undated (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Program info, Undated (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Putting the Demo Back in Democracy - flyers and press, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Queeruption distribution flyer, Undated (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Ramapo College brochure - PTTV article, Undated (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Schedules (1 of 3), Undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Schedules (2 of 3), Undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Schedules (3 of 3), Undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Schedule flyers, Undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Schedules, flyers, etc..., Undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - "Schedule masters / schedule related shit", Undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Screening and schedule info, Undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Shows by Women, Undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Storm from the Mountains - flyers, Undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - T-shirt art, Undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - T-shirt / tape order form flyer, Undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Wexner show programs, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - What is PTTV binder, Undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Xerox original flyers, Undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Year of the Tiger party, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Series IV: Financial Material
  This series contains the financial material from Paper Tiger TV. It includes bills, bank statements, grant applications, and all other financial papers.
  - Grants - NEA, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Bookkeeping, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Check stubs, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Chemical Bank withdrawals, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Citibank account info and statements, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Citibank - cancelled checks, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Grants, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Grants - NYSCAq, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - NYSCA - supplementary application form, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Accounting, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Budget, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Check stubs, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Chemical Bank - statements, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Citibank - statements, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Receipts paid (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Receipts paid (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Check stubs, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Chemical Bank - statements, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Insurance - equipment, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Invoices - tapes, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Accounting ledgers, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Check stubs, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Deep Dish TV directory sales, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Deep Dish TV income, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Invoices - tapes, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Ledger of expenses, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Orders - PTTV West, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Phone invoices, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Tax exempt status form, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Budget, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Budget - Deep Dish TV, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Check stubs, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Chemical Bank - statements, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Deep Dish TV - finances, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Grants, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Invoices - tapes, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Ledger of receipts and disbursments, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Orders complete (1 of 3), 1987 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Orders complete (2 of 3), 1987 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Orders complete (3 of 3), 1987 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Paper Tiger / Deep Dish distribution list, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Petty cash, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Petty cash, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Petty cash, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Receipts, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Receipts paid, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Receipts paid, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Budget, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Budget - Deep Dish TV, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Check stubs, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Deep Dish TV finances, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Grants, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Invoices - tapes, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Ledgers, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Ledger of disbursment, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Budget, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Check stubs, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Complete orders (1 of 3), 1989 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Complete orders (2 of 3), 1989 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Complete orders (3 of 3), 1989 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Grants, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Grants - Benton Foundation, FIVF, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Grants - Puffin Foundation, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Grant report, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Invoices - tapes, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Loan agreements, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Orders - PTTV West, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Budget, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Check stubs, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Complete orders (1 of 3), 1990 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Complete orders (2 of 3), 1990 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Complete orders (3 of 3), 1990 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Grants, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Grant report, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Grants - Andy Warhol Foundation, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Grants - Mid-Atlantic Visual Arts, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Invoices - tapes, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - NYCCRM - franchise negotiations, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Orders - PTTV West, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Rental invoice - electronics, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Bills, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Bills - TCN, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Bills - UPS (for GCTV), 1991 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Budget, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Fed-Ex receipts, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Financial report, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Grants, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Invoices - tapes, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Ledger book - GCTV, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Tape sales / rentals, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Bills, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Bills - TCN, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Budget, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Grants, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Grants - Art Matters Inc., 1992 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Grants - DCA, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Grants - NAMAC, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Grants - NEA, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Grants - The New York Community Trust, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Grants - NY Foundation for the Arts, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - International sales, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Invoices, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Invoices - tapes, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Receipts - shipping, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Bills, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Bills - TCN, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Budget, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Grants, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Grants - Manhattan Neighborhood Network, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Grants - NAMAC, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Grants - NEA, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Invoices, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Invoices - tape sales, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Receipts, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Bills, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Bills - TCN, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Budget, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Donations, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Grants, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Grants - NAMAC, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Grants - NEA, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Grants - NEH Media Alliance, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Grants - NY Council on the Humanities, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Grants - Paul Robeson Fund, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Invoices, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Invoices - tape sales, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Orders - PTTV West, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Receipts - shipping, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Biils, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Budget, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Distribution (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Distribution (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Grants, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Grants - DCA, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Grants - Funding Exchange emergency grant info, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Insurance, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Insurance - old, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Invoices, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Invoices, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Invoices - Signal to Noise, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Invoices - tape sales, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Receipts - shipping, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Sales - Refunds and credits, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Taxes, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Bills, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Budget, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Grants - DCA, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Insurance, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - International sales, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Invoices, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Invoices - Media Alliance, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Invoices - tapes, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Receipts, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Amalgamated Bank - check stubs, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Bills, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Bills - NYNEX / Bell Atlantic, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Budget, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Complete invoice, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Grant - DCA, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Grant - Paul Robeson Fund / Funding Exchange, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Grant - MNN Revolving, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Grant - NYFA Community Assets, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Insurance, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - International sales, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Invoices, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Invoices - tapes, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Invoices - TCN, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Invoices - Wallace's Bookstore, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Receipts, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Record of Borrowing and invoices, 1997-2001 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - USPS - 3602N form, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - A.J. Muste - Fiscal sponsorship, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Amalgamated Bank - check stubs, 1998-2000 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Bills, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Bills - NYNEX / Bell Atlantic, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Budget - Northstar workshop, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Certificate of incorporation, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Charity registration forms, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Complete invoice (1 of 4), 1998 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Complete invoice (2 of 4), 1998 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Complete invoice (3 of 4), 1998 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Complete invoice (4 of 4), 1998 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Financial material, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Grants, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Grants - DCA, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Grants - North Star Fund, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Grants - Paul Robeson Fund, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Insurance, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Invoices, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Invoices - TCN, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Member reimbursements, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Receipts, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Volunteer Lawyers for the Arts, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Winnie Tam and Co. - PTTV financial info, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Accountant file, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Accountant's review report, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Bank reconciliations, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Bills - Bell Atlantic, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Bills paid (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Bills paid (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Bills - TCN, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Book keeping, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Complete invoices (1 of 4), 1999 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Complete invoices (2 of 4), 1999 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Complete invoices (3 of 4), 1999 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Complete invoices (4 of 4), 1999 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Donations, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Financial statement, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Grants, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Grants - Albert A. List Foundation, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Grants - List Foundation grant agreement, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Grants - MacArthur, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Grants - Open Society Institute, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Insurance, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Invoice - orders, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Member reimbursements, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Petty cash, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Receipts, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Winnie Tam and Co. - "Ask Winnie", 1999 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Winnie Tam and Co. - services proposed, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Accounting, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Bank reconciliations, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Bills - Citibank, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Bills paid (1 of 2), 2000 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Bills paid (2 of 2), 2000 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Bills - TCN, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Budget, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Check stubs, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Citibank - charges by category, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Citibank - credit increase, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Citibank - quarterly reports, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Credit info for PTTV, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Expenses - Jan-April, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Expenses - May-August, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Expenses - Sept-Dec, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Grants, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Grants - MacArthur agreement, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Grants - MNN, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Grants - North Star application, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Grants - NYFA, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Grants - Open Society Institute, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Insurance, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Invoice file - Freedom Archives, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Invoices - tape orders, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Receipts, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Reciepts - miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Receipts - petty cash, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Reimbursement - Pacific Film Archive, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Budget - Treasury, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Check stubs, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Citibank - annual account summary, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Citibank - quarterly account summary, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Endorsment - Access Orbit, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Expenses, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Expenses - Sept-Dec, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Finances, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Fenced Out - distribution, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Grants, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Grants - DCA, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Grants - Experimental Television Center, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Grants - general overview, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Grants - MCAF agreements, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Grants - MNN reports and agreements, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Grants - North Star, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Grants - NYCH, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Grants - NYFA, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Grants - NYSCA application form, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Grants - Resist application, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Invoices (1 of 2), 2001 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Invoices (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Invoices - tape sales, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Invoices - tape orders, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Payroll reports (1 of 2), 2001 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Payroll reports (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Receipts - car rental, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Receipts - Citibank, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Reimbursement - Lightwork, Access Orbit, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Tax returns, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Winnie Tam and Co. - Annual report, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Winnie Tam and Co - audit, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Bills, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Citibank - business card expenses, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Expenses - Jan-June, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Expenses - July-Dec, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Fundraising - Queeruption, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Financial report, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Grants, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Grants - A.J. Muste, 9/11 Emergency Funds, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Grants - Funding Exchange, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Grants - MNN application, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Grants - MNN, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Grants - NYSCA, general operations agreement and contract, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Grants - North Star, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Grants - North Star application, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Winnie Tam and Co - financial materials, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Winnie Tam and Co - Mid-year financial report, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Citibank - quarterly report, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Citibank - statements, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Donors, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Expenses - Jan-May, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Expenses - June-Dec, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Financial statements, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Grants, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Grants - DCA, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Grants - MNN, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Grants - NYSCA, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Grants - NYSCA exhibition funds, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Grants - NYSCA preservation funds, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Invoices - tape requests, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Invoices - tape sales and workshops, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Sales - tapes, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Grants, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Grants - Funding Exchange Emergency Grant, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Grants - North Star Fund, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Invoices - tape sales and workshops, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Sales - tapes (1 of 3), 2004 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Sales - tapes (2 of 3), 2004 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Sales - tapes (3 of 3), 2004 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Bills - UPS, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Grants, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 13)